Alec, are you really alright now?
Alek, ta blessure va vraiment bien ?
I'm fine.
Oui.
More importantly, we need to get to work on those potions.
Mais pour le moment, concentrons nous sur ces potions.
There's not much time.
Tu n'as plus beaucoup de temps.
I'll help supply you with the magic you need.
Je vais te donne du mana.
I did it!
J'ai réussi !
That's it.
Continue comme ça.
Yeah!
Oui !
But this is… How should I put it…?
Mais… quand il me donne du mana…
When he gives me his magic, I feel hot all over…
j'ai l'impresssion d'être dans ses bras…
Loneal…
Lonile…
You did great.
Bon travail.
I shouldn't be thinking such things when he's only trying to help…
Pourquoi je réagis comme ça… Il ne fait que m'aider…
There doesn't seem to be any issues with the quality or quantity.
Niveau quantité et qualité, pas de problèmes.
I'm not particularly happy about it but… your club is allowed to continue activities.
Je suis encore un peu fâché, mais ton club peut continuer d'exister.
Thank you!
Merci !
I finally… finished it…
C'est fait…
Loneal, are you alright?
Lonile, ça va ?
Alec…
Alek…
I'm… fine…
Je… vais bien.
Why is your face all flushed? Did he do something to you?
Qu'est-ce qui t'arrives ? Il s'est passé quelque chose avec lui ?
N-No! Earlier, when you gave me your magic…
Non… Quand tu m'as donné du mana…
it felt like you were holding me, and…
C'était comme si… tu me prenais dans tes bras…
That's why…
Donc…
I see.
Je vois.
If this is my fault, then I will gladly take responsibility.
Si c'est ma faute, je suis heureux d'en prendre la responsabilité.
Prepare yourself, Loneal.
Je vais te prendre.
Your Highness… But that's…!
Prince…
This isn't right… What about Lily…?
On ne devrait pas… Pense à Lili…
This is a type of emergency treatment.
je ne fais que te soigner.
Emergency… treatment?
Me soigner ?
Your symptoms are probably a reaction to my magic.
Ma mana chamboule ton corps.
So, I need to help you release the pent-up energy… as a form of treatment.
Pour te soigner… je dois expulser cette énergie.
Let me help.
Je fais ça pour t'aider.
Good boy, Loneal.
Voilà, comme ça.
Did you cum just from me putting it in?
Je l'ai à peine mise et tu as déjà joui ?
I can't get over how sensitive you are. I love it.
Tu es tellement sensible… C'est adorable.
I want to see you… come undone even more, Loneal.
Laisse-toi aller.
It's as though… you were made… just for me…
Je suis heureux que nos corps soient compatibles.
It feels… way too good…
C'est… si bon…
You're so…
Tu es tellement…
I know you're only doing this to help, but…
Tu fais ça pour m'aider… Mais…
It's making me… lose control…!
C'est trop bon et ça me rend fou…
Yeah… I can feel you clenching down all around me…
Je peux te sentir te contracter autour de moi.
Alec… I can't stop moaning…!
Je n'arrive pas à retenir ma voix…
Too much, it's too much… I'm about to…!
C'est trop… ça me fait tout bizarre…
I can… feel you… filling me up…
Tu m'as… rempli…
I love you… Loneal.
Lonile. Je t'aime.
Y-Your Highness… What's all this?
Alek, c'est pour quoi tout ça ?
It's to celebrate you doing such a good job on all those potions.
C'est pour célébrer ton succès avec les potions.
But more importantly, are you feeling alright?
Sinon, ton corps va mieux ?
Ah, um… Y-Yes…
Oui !
That's it! I could use the same method to make the antidote…!
C'est vrai ! Je pourrais utiliser cette méthode pour faire l'antidote !
An antidote?
Un antidote ?
Why would you need to make something like that?
Pourquoi faire ?
I can't say it's because I used a love potion on you…
Je ne peux pas lui dire que c'est parce que je l'ai renversé avec une potion d'amour…
Just as I thought. He really is a genius when it comes to making potions.
Il est vraiment doué pour faire des potions.
A love potion, huh?
Une potion d'amour…
I-ls such a thing actually possible!?
Q-Quoi ? C'est possible ?
No, this kind of naming is something he does to amuse himself.
Non, c'est un blague.
It's just a formula for your average stimulant.
Il a juste mixé plusieurs aphrodisiaques ensemble.
It wouldn't have any effect on someone who's not already interested.
Ça n'aurait aucut effet sur quelqu'un qui n'est pas déjà attiré.
I have to hurry and turn him back!
Je dois me dépêcher de corriger ça !
Y-Your Highness… Wh-What about the food?
Prince… la nourriture va…
Are you by any chance, hiding something from me, Loneal?
Est-ce que tu me caches quelque chose ?
How about I have you take your time and explain, hmm?
Et si tu me disais tout ?
You Highness…!
Prince… !